[
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"A bridge hand with no cards in one suit is said to have a _______.", "answer":0, "answers":["Void"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"A poker hand consisting of three of a kind and a pair is called a _______.", "answer":0, "answers":["Full house"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"A Royal Flush is the best hand you can get in which game", "answer":0, "answers":["Poker"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"A.k.a a pair of aces & a pair of eights", "answer":0, "answers":["Dead mans hand"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"Atari competitor that featured better graphics.", "answer":0, "answers":["Intellevision"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"Board game involving rapid climbing and tragic sliding.", "answer":0, "answers":["Chutes(Snakes) and ladders"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"Building tool named after Civil War president.", "answer":0, "answers":["Lincoln logs"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"Charles Darrow based his game upon the 1904 \"The Landlord's Game\".", "answer":0, "answers":["Monopoly"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"D&D stands for this.", "answer":0, "answers":["Dungeons and dragons"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"Eva Gabor and Johnny Carson popularized this game by climbing over each other.", "answer":0, "answers":["Twister"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"Frank Lloyd Wright son John invented these after watching workers move timber.", "answer":0, "answers":["Lincoln logs"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"From what were balloons originally made?", "answer":0, "answers":["Animal bladders"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"How many balls are used in a game of snooker in addition to the cue ball", "answer":0, "answers":["21"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"How many balls are used in a game of snooker including the cue ball?", "answer":0, "answers":["22"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"How many discs does each player have to start with in draughts (checkers)", "answer":0, "answers":["12"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"How many dots are on a twister mat?", "answer":0, "answers":["Thirty"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"How many dots are there on a pair of dice", "answer":0, "answers":["42"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"How many dots are there on a pair of dice?", "answer":0, "answers":["Forty two"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"How many folds does a Monopoly board have?", "answer":0, "answers":["One"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"How many numbers are on the spinner in the game of 'Life'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Ten"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"How many pieces are found in a chess set ?", "answer":0, "answers":["32"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"How many squares are there on a chessboard", "answer":0, "answers":["64"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"How many squares are there on a chessboard?", "answer":0, "answers":["64"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"How many tiles does a player play to score a bingo in Scrabble", "answer":0, "answers":["7"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"How much does Park Place cost in Monopoly (in US Dollars)?", "answer":0, "answers":["450"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"How much is the luxury tax (in dollars) in Monopoly", "answer":0, "answers":["75"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"If you \"peg out\" what game are you playing?\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Cribbage"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"If you combined k & p to make cables what would your hobby be", "answer":0, "answers":["Knitting"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"If you're involved in firing, throwing, and glazing, what do you do", "answer":0, "answers":["Pottery"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"In a game of horseshoes, how many feet apart must the stakes be?", "answer":0, "answers":["Forty"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"In Monopoly, What is the cost to buy Electric Company", "answer":0, "answers":["150"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"In Monopoly, What is the cost to buy New York Avenue", "answer":0, "answers":["200"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"In Monopoly, What is the cost to buy Oriental Avenue", "answer":0, "answers":["100"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"In Monopoly, What is the cost to buy Vermont Avenue", "answer":0, "answers":["100"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"In Monopoly, What is the cost to Get Out of Jail", "answer":0, "answers":["50"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"In poker five cards of the same suit is called a(n) __________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Flush"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"In poker five cards of the same suit is called a(n) ________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Flush"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"In pool, what color is the eight ball", "answer":0, "answers":["Black"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"In pool, what color is the eight ball?", "answer":0, "answers":["Black"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"In roulette, what number is green?", "answer":0, "answers":["Zero"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"In snooker, how many points are accumulated in a perfect break?", "answer":0, "answers":["147"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"In the game of chess, which piece has the most freedom to move?", "answer":0, "answers":["Queen"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"In this card game, teams are designated North_South and East_West.", "answer":0, "answers":["Bridge"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"In this game players take turns placing disks on an 8x8 board.", "answer":0, "answers":["Othello"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"In which game might a person have a \"full house\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Poker"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"In which game or sport are \"Staunton\" pieces used?\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Chess"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"In which game or sport can a person be \"skunked\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Cribbage"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"In which sport are terms \"spare\" and \"gutter\" used?\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Tenpin bowling"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"In which sport or game are the terms: 'pin', 'fork', and 'skewer' used?", "answer":0, "answers":["Chess"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"In which sport or game is the term \"rook\" used?\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Chess"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"Klondike is the most popular form of this game.", "answer":0, "answers":["Solitaire"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"Large plastic animals gobbled marbles in this game.", "answer":0, "answers":["Hungry hungry hippos"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"Leading manufacturer of toy cars.", "answer":0, "answers":["Hot wheels"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"Little blue cartoon figurines.", "answer":0, "answers":["Smurfs"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"Monopoly penalty space between Baltic Ave. and Reading RR (2 wds)", "answer":0, "answers":["Income tax"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"Moving anti-clockwise on a dartboard, what is the number next to '4'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Eighteen"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"Mundane toy that involved sticking plastic pieces on scenes.", "answer":0, "answers":["Colorforms"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"Name of Barbie's hot pink sports_car.", "answer":0, "answers":["Vette"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"Name the only flexible murder weapon in the game of \"Cluedo\".", "answer":0, "answers":["Rope"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"Name the only woman suspect in the game of \"Cluedo\" who isn't married.\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Miss scarlett"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"Number of points lost for scratching off the blue ball in snooker", "answer":0, "answers":["5"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"Originally an exercise ring, Indonesia banned it as \"might stimulate passion\".", "answer":0, "answers":["Hula hoop"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"Personal merry_go_round guaranteed to make you dizzy.", "answer":0, "answers":["Sit n spin"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"Plastic vehicle equipped with spin_out brake.", "answer":0, "answers":["Big wheel"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"Talking toy that helped you do well on Spelling tests.", "answer":0, "answers":["Speak n spell"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"Term for any number between 19 & 36 in Roulette", "answer":0, "answers":["Passe"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"Term for any number between one & 18 in Roulette", "answer":0, "answers":["Manque"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"The easiest to defend continent in Risk", "answer":0, "answers":["Australia"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"The King in chess can move a maximum of this many squares.", "answer":0, "answers":["Two"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"The object of this card game is to meld sets of 7 or more cards.", "answer":0, "answers":["Canasta"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"There are this many red_letter cubes in Perquackey.", "answer":0, "answers":["3"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"These are the two highest valued letters in \"Scrabble\".  \"Q\" and _____.\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Z"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"These are the two highest valued letters in \"Scrabble\". \"Q\" and _____.\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Z"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"This ancient Chinese game is played with 156 small rectangular tiles.", "answer":0, "answers":["Mah jongg"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"This chess term means \"in passing\"", "answer":0, "answers":["En passant"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"This cube puzzle was invented by a Hungarian mathematician in 1974.", "answer":0, "answers":["Rubik"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"This game (involving a net) was introduced in 1874 as sphairistike", "answer":0, "answers":["Tennis"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"This game of chance was originally called 'Beano'.", "answer":0, "answers":["Bingo"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"This is a French named car_racing card game.", "answer":0, "answers":["Mille borne"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"This is the game that \"Ties you up in knots\".", "answer":0, "answers":["Twister"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"This is the length, in feet, of a regulation Snooker table", "answer":0, "answers":["12"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"This is the lowest ranking suit in Bridge.", "answer":0, "answers":["Clubs"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"This is the oldest board game still played (5000 yr old boards were found)", "answer":0, "answers":["Backgammon"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"This is the strongest poker hand you can get.", "answer":0, "answers":["Royal flush"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"This popular card game's name is spanish for \"one.\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Uno"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"This term denotes a chess move in which both the king and the rook are moved.", "answer":0, "answers":["Castling"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"Tic-Tac-Toe is based on which game ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Nine men morris"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"To what do opposite faces of a dice always add up?", "answer":0, "answers":["Seven"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"What are a cheesboard's vertical rows called?", "answer":0, "answers":["Files"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"What are a chessboard's horizontal rows called?", "answer":0, "answers":["Ranks"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"What bowling term means three straight strikes?", "answer":0, "answers":["Turkey"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"What does a twitcher look for", "answer":0, "answers":["Birds"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"What game is Bobby Fischer associated with?", "answer":0, "answers":["Chess"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"What game or sport is Bobby Fischer identified with?", "answer":0, "answers":["Chess"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"What is another name for the card game 'Blackjack'?", "answer":0, "answers":["21"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"What is another name for the card game 'Twenty-one'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Blackjack"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"What is the best possible score in blackjack?", "answer":0, "answers":["21"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"What is the Chess ranking system called ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Elo"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"What is the most popular sport in england?", "answer":0, "answers":["Darts"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"What is the name of the board that Baduk is player on ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Goban"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"What is the tallest piece on a chessboard?", "answer":0, "answers":["King"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"What number is at 12 o'clock on a dartboard?", "answer":0, "answers":["20"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"What number is on the opposite side of the \"five\" on dice?", "answer":0, "answers":["Two"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"What score is not possible for a cribbage hand", "answer":0, "answers":["19"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"What score is not possible for a cribbage hand?", "answer":0, "answers":["Nineteen"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"What toy was originally made from the bladder of an animal?", "answer":0, "answers":["Balloon"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"What would you buy from a Gibbons' catalogue", "answer":0, "answers":["Stamps"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"Where did the card game 'bridge' originate?", "answer":0, "answers":["Turkey"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"Where does the annual Poker World Series take place?", "answer":0, "answers":["Las Vegas"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"Where on your body would you wear flippers", "answer":0, "answers":["Feet"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"Which British game is known as checkers in the USA", "answer":0, "answers":["Draughts"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"Which chess piece is usually valued as 5 points", "answer":0, "answers":["Rook"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"Which chess piece is usually valued as 5 points?", "answer":0, "answers":["Rook"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"Which exercises are designed to increase O2 consumption & speed circulation", "answer":0, "answers":["Aerobics"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"Which game has 361 intersections ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Go"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"Which game usually begins with, \"Is it animal, vegetable, or mineral\"", "answer":0, "answers":["20 questions"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"Whist is an early form of this card game.", "answer":0, "answers":["Bridge"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"Whose 3_dimensional cube became a 70s & 80s craze", "answer":0, "answers":["Rubiks cube"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"Word derived from \"shah mat\", from the arabic for \"the king is dead\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Checkmate"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"You inserted sticks into round blocks to build abstractions with these.", "answer":0, "answers":["Tinker toys"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"You meld groups of three cards or more of the same rank or suit in this game.", "answer":0, "answers":["Rummy"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TOYS_AND_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TOYS_AND_GAMES"], "question":"You rotated blocks and matched up the colors to solve this puzzle.", "answer":0, "answers":["Rubiks cube"], "source":""}
]